

Su Su Sandi

Junior Full Stack Developer



Professional Summary

Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Handles any part of process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 4 years of related experience.



Technical Profile

•HTML	•React	•Android	•AJAX
•CSS	React Native	•Laravel	•Golang
JavaScript	•Java	•C	•Git, SVN
•PHP	PostgreSOL/MvSal	•XMI.	



Employment

Junior Android Developer DIR-ACE Technology, Yangon

- •Developed mobile application for Agent, Client and website for Admin panel of AEON Microfinance (Myanmar) with PrimeFaces and Android.
- •Created UT spec, IT spec and Test Evidence files for AEON Microfinance (Myanmar) project.

Senior Full Stack Developer DIR-ACE Technology, Yangon

- •Developed Venture Health Care(diabetes food management for pregnant women) mobile application for Japan client with React Native and firebase.
- •Modified JCL code request from Japan and create VBA tools for review ledger and other management.
- •Developed Toyota Project(check which zone is available for car parking, scan car bar code information and take evidence picture).
- •Modified Job Arranger Manager(is an open source job scheduler for ZABBIX) project with PHP in Agile.
- •Developed new version of Job Arranger Manager project for ZABBIX using ReactJS and PHP for 1 year in Agile.
- •Developed Proxy Connector for ZABBIX with Golang in Agile.
- •Contributed ideas and suggestions in team meetings and delivered updates on deadlines, designs and enhancements.

Contact



susus and i. dev@gmail.com



https://sususand.github.io



+959 951 402 302



No.1, Than Lan Street, Hlaing



Myanmar 11051



WhatsApp:+959951402302

Jul-2019 ~ Apr 2020

Apr 2020 ~ Aug 2022



Education

Jun 2014 ~ Mar 2020

Bachelor of Computer Science B.C.Sc

University of Computer Studies, Meiktila

Hard Skills

•Programming Languages, StarUML, Java, C++, PHP, SE, SAD, DBMS, AI, Data Structure, OJT

Soft Skills

•Presentation skill, Team corporation skills, Communication skills, Leadership skills

Samsung Android Training Course

University of Computer Studies, Mandalay

•Basic android application development , Activity Lifecycle, API integration, Package Development



Internship

May 2019 ~ Jul 2019

Dec 2015 ~ Jan 2016

DIR-ACE Technology, Yangon

•Created Student Management System with Spring Framework and Learned on Unit Test Specification creation.



Courses

Feb 2019 ~ Apr 2019

Advance Android Training Course

•Created some mini mobile applications and practice on API with Firebase.

Jun 2018 ~ Jul 2018

Youth Leadership & Development

•Covered leadership and management

Jul 2017

Information Technology Passport Examination



Hobbies







